iplpower.com 2011-12-09

# Indianapolis Power & Light Co.

Privacy Policy 

Revision:  June 1, 2007

Indianapolis Power & Light Company (IPL) is committed to protecting our customers' privacy. When you visit IPLpower.com, our Web server automatically recognizes your domain name, but not the e-mail address. This enables us to collect information on what pages consumers visit.  Personal information is only collected when you volunteer it by typing in your information and is generally used for IPL to fulfill a request like a service connection or change, bill payment, etc.

 **Cookies  
** The IPL Web site, IPLpower.com, uses “cookies,” which are small pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow us to manage aspects of your account across our Web site. If you select the option for IPLpower.com to remember your username and password, a cookie file will be stored on your hard drive after you log in. This allows us to re-populate your username and password on our login form, saving you the trouble of remembering it. You can choose to de-select this option at any time, which will delete the cookie file after you log in. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your Web browser to not accept cookies. By not accepting cookies, pages of this Web site that use cookies may not fully function and you may not be able to access certain information on this Web site.

Use of IP Addresses  
Whenever you surf the Web, an Internet Protocol (IP) address/number is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider (ISP). When you visit IPLpower.com, our servers log your IP address. IPL collects IP addresses for system administration and to analyze the use of this Web site. Data gathered from logging your IP address is not tied to your personal information and is not used to identify you.

We may use your IP address in cooperation with your Internet service provider to identify you if we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use Agreement, protect our services or customers, or comply with laws or regulations.

 **Release of Information**  
Upon a customer’s request, IPL will share information with other local utility companies for credit purposes only. IPL uses an external credit reporting agency to determine credit-worthiness.  
We have established security procedures to ensure that information is being shared only with authorized representatives.  

Occasionally, we may hire third parties to act on our behalf for activities such as market research surveys, billing, technical support or contest entry processing. These parties will not be permitted to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing their specific services, and they are not permitted to disclose, transfer or sell personally identifiable information.

 **Supplementation of Information**   
To fulfill our service obligations, we may supplement the information we receive from you when you request a service with information from outside sources.  For example, when you request electric service we will use your name and social security number to verify your identity and credit history.

 **E-mail**  
IPL collects e-mail addresses to be able to quickly contact you regarding services or items you’ve requested and topics about which you have expressed interest.  If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by e-mailing us at [Webmaster.IPL@AES.com](mailto:Webmaster.IPL@AES.com).  We will remove your name from our e-mail list for those purposes.  However, IPL reserves the right to contact you via e-mail if deemed necessary for administrative or emergency purposes.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses related to our business but not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. 

IPL strives to make our Web site secure by using industry-standard encryption technologies when electronically transferring and receiving customer information through the Web site.  We have appropriate measures and policies in place at all of our locations to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information collected at our Web site. However, information transmitted via e-mail is NOT secure or encrypted.  Remember, it may be possible for an unauthorized person to gain access to your information despite our security measures. Therefore, you enter information in this Web site at your own risk.

You should be careful and responsible when you are online and maintain the secrecy of any passwords and account information you have regarding this Web site. In addition, you should use up-to-date virus scanning software on your computer to reduce the risk of encountering a virus through e-mails.  IPL accepts no responsibility or liability for any loss or damage arising from the use of e-mail or their attachments, or for any viruses or errors or delays in the contents that result from e-mail transmissions.

 **Policy Changes  
** Any changes to this IPL policy will be posted on the Web site.  IPL reserves the right to change this policy at any time and encourages you to periodically review this policy for any such changes. Your continued use of this Web site means that you have read, understood and agreed to be bound by the current policy posted on the Web site at the time of your visit. 

**Updating Your Contact Information  
** IPL customers can update their contact information by calling us at (317) 261-8222 or sending an e-mail message to [CustomerServices@aes.com](mailto:CustomerServices@aes.com).  You must include your IPL account number to change information.

For more detailed contact information, click here.
